this exercise
asks us to create a new directory named
my folder
my command line prompt displays my
current working directory
which is a folder called exercises
i can use the ls command to display the
contents of this directory
and you can see that right now it's
empty
to create a new directory
we can use mkdir
and give it the name of our new
directory which we'll call
myfolder now when we view the contents
of our current directory
we can see that new directory there so
let's navigate into this folder
using the cd command which you can think
of
as change directory
and we'll use ls to look at the contents
of this folder as well
and it's empty so let's create a couple
of new files
we'll do this using touch
we'll create a ruby file 1.rb
and a second ruby file 2.rb
now when we examine the contents of my
folder
we see our two new files there the
exercise tells us that we want
each of our ruby files to output a
message to the user when we run them
so let's hop over to our text editor
i've accessed the new directory
my folder within the text editor and
opened up each of the two ruby files we
created
i just want to output a simple message
to the user
this is file one
jumping back to our command line
let's run this file
and we see the expected output
so we should be able to do something
very similar for our second file as well
and again we see that output
you